All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I will be the king of the pirates!
In the two years that have passed since the War of the Best in Marineford, the Straw Hat Pirates underwent special training before returning to the Sabaody Archipelago.
Now, in order to progress to the New World, Luffy and his crew have arrived at Fishman Island, thousands of feet below sea level.
However, they were attacked by the new Fishman Pirates, causing them to become separated yet again.
In this time of need, Mermaids managed to rescue some of the crew and bring them safely to Kami's home.
Now, what did I do?
We don't have time! Guys, this is serious!
Please, I'm begging you! Whatever it takes! I can't let my friend die!
The Fishman Island will be annihilated? Charlie's prophecy!
We need help! My friend is dying! Can anyone give him blood?
Human or Fishman, SRH- is his type!
He doesn't have much time! Please, we're begging you!
Help him!
Poor thing. I'm sorry. This is a bad place for a human to get a blood transfusion.
But, I'm sure Luffy Chin and your friends will figure something out.
Damn it! No matter who we ask, there isn't anyone here who will give him blood! Come on!
I refuse to give up! Sanji's counting on us!
There's gotta be somebody!
Oh, right! Luffy! I found some humans here!
Hey, that barrel over there is the one that drifted in with all Kami's friends, right?
What's in it? Maybe... treasure?
Uh...
I don't know. It's sealed pretty tightly, so it's gotta be important.
Yeah? I think we should open it.
Me too. What if it needs to go in the fridge?
Good point.
Wow. Talk about well prepared.
Way to go!
Hey, Sanji! Are you awake?
Talk to us!
Where am I?
You pulled through!
We're safe in a town right by the harbor. I was scared.
You almost lost all the blood in your body.
I was starting to think we'd never find you a donor. That was a real close call.
That so? Wow.
What in the hell happened... to me?
You shouldn't be sitting up so quickly. You need to rest.
I just don't get it. I mean, the fish could have given blood. But no, instead we had to run all over town looking for another human. Which took forever.
I know, right? I was starting to lose hope there.
I'm sorry. I appreciate what you did, though. But I just don't remember much. Why'd this happen? Where was I and what was I doing? When I think about it, it's all a big blip.
Ah! No! Let it go already!
If you try to force the memories, you could relapse!
Oh, yeah. I almost forgot, Sanji. You haven't met your donors. So here, say hi. And also thank you.
Wait. Could my savior have been... a dainty girl?
Don't worry. We're only human. After all, if we don't look out for each other, who will?
Don't worry, babe. If you want, we can give you more.
Looks like he's back to his old self.
That's not exactly gratitude.
Luffy?
Can I see the cut on your arm for a second, please?
Huh?
It's positive.
Thought so. Luffy, that wound's poisonous.
Oh, wow. Really? That must have been the sting I felt earlier.
One of the fish men got me.
You don't seem poisoned. You feeling okay?
Yeah.
Either way, we should be careful.
This stuff's probably deadly. You sure you're all right?
Yep.
Wow. So weird. It sounds crazy. But you must have somehow developed an antibody to fight against this kind of stuff.
Tell me, have you ever experienced a poisoning like this in the past?
Let's see.
Yeah. Back when I was at Impel Down, I almost got killed that way.
That is not funny at all.
Yeah, it is. I bet it was that octopus swordsman. I mean, he blocked my punch, so he's gotta be strong. No prob. Next time, I'll be ready.
Huh?
They're so loud. I think that came from by that cove. Don't care. I've got bigger problems. These guys are messed up real bad. And what's worse, Straw Hat got poisoned too. I'm dead if he dies.
I'm positive I heard their screams come from here. Ishili! Where are you?
This is where I saw them last. But where in the world could they have gone?
Did anyone else hear them say something about opening up a barrel?
Hey, Luffy-chin, Usopp-chin, come here. There's someone I'd like you to meet.
Huh?
She's the owner of this place. She okayed Sanji resting here. The Madam Charlie.
Cool. Thanks and stuff.
Has the blonde boy's condition improved at all?
Yep. But it's best he doesn't meet you because you're so beautiful. Right? That would be bad. Also, we probably shouldn't tell him he's in the back of the mermaid cafe. Not if we want him to get well.
Why keep it a secret?
Cuz doctor's orders. Chakra's pretty sure that if Sanji-chin finds out, he's gonna have a bad relapse.
What a strange prognosis.
Hey, big lady! Fish lady!
Wow, that was rude. Come on.
Tell me what this is.
It's beautiful.
It's also not on the list of things you're allowed to touch.
Huh? Oh, that? You're looking at Madam Charlie's crystal ball. With it, she can see the future. Her precognitive visions are why she's famous.
Well, it used to be. Not anymore.
Huh?
The future isn't ours to know, right?
Sounds rough. Oh, by the way, how do mermaids take a dump?
We are not talking about mermaid poop again!
Don't you have any class?
Guys, apologize! Quickly!
Sorry.
Why don't you take the rest of the day off, Kami? I think your friends would appreciate a tour of the island.
Really? You sure?
It's fine. You deserve it, seeing as you're always working so hard.
Besides, business has been slow with human guests so uncommon these days. So we have to be extra good hosts.
The girls from the cove should show up soon. Then we'll have more hands around here than a starfish.
More than... starfish?
Oh, that's right! Crap! I should've already delivered Papa Goose clams by now!
Wow. I have no idea what's going on.
I bet he's getting mad waiting for his food.
Not quite. He's enjoying the cafe. An old friend of his suddenly came into town, and they've been living it up since he arrived.
Wait. He's here?
Well, that makes things easy.
I didn't want to bring this up in front of her, but Madam told me a lot of stories from when she was little.
She said in those days human pirates came to the island all the time.
But that was quite a while ago. About a year before the Great Pirate Era began.
It's hard for her to talk about things sometimes, especially when she foresees bad stuff like the war at Marineford and Whitebeard's death.
What?!
Can you imagine knowing something horrible will happen that you can't stop?
That must be terrifying!
Hey, where's Chopper?
Oh, he said he was gonna hang out here and look after Sanji.
Come on, you two! Hurry up!
Kay!
Right now we're on what's considered Coral Hill's main street. And that is the primary entrance to the Mermaid Cafe!
Man, thought I was gonna starve to death.
They might only serve snacks.
No, you're good. We've got cakes and sea fruit too!
And meat?
Uh, no. We merfolk don't really eat meat and fish. But we have wakame brulee, mozuku tarts, kelp souffle...
You call that food?
Wait! We do have some meat!
From shellfish! Scallop sandwiches, plant pizza, and...
Those give me the bad name! Stop talking!
Whoa! Okay, be cool. Let's just go inside.
Yeah, let's all go find Papagu.
Shellfish! What the hell kind of crab is that?!
Thank you very much!
Yeah!
Time to give the dogfish a bone.
Gotta love the fins, huh?
Oh, wow! It's Brooke!
Hooray!
Huh?
Luffy and Usopp?
And Kami, you've become such a lovely young lady!
Now, may I please see your panties?
Mermaids don't wear those!
Hey, guys!
You have no idea how much I've missed you!
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
Hey, Papagu! Sorry it's been so long!
I guess that makes you Papagu's old friend we heard about!
Yes, though...
I've missed you!
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
Hey, Papagu! Sorry it's been so long!
I guess that makes you Papagu's old friend we heard about!
Yes, though...
I wish the reunion had better circumstances,
because without him I'd be sunk!
Don't let the laugh fool you!
He means that literally!
There I was, hard at work by the cove,
finalizing a design idea I had,
when all of a sudden,
a pile of bones went drifting by on a log!
Huh?
Bone Daddy!
Come see us again, K?
I had a great time, Soul King!
I'll be back, lovely ladies!
Lots of bones to go around!
What?!
Oh, I've gone limp!
No, I haven't!
Skeletons are always rigid!
Good thing I'm already dead,
or I would probably die of embarrassment right now!
Oh, you!
This cafe's really put Brooke in rare form!
Yeah, whatever's going on inside must be awesome!
Hold up there, boss!
Huh?
What are you in such a hurry for?
I know you're interested in the cafe,
and I get that,
but it's not like it's going anywhere!
Let's come back when you have your whole crew!
Bone Daddy and I were just about to head back to my place!
Why don't you guys come with us?
If you do,
you can eat all the Sea King meat you want!
Did you say meat?!
Yeah, I did!
I'm a wild animal, you feel me?
It's not like I eat boring shellfish!
I need food with a little more bite!
Sea Monster Exclusive Diet!
Oh!
By the way,
I brought your order of clams!
Sweet!
My favorite treat is finally here!
Ha!
Oh!
So much for your diet!
Oh, man!
Beautiful mermaid!
Yes!
Ah!
Lovely mermaids!
So sweet!
You okay, hun?!
Ah!
Lovely mermaids!
So sweet!
You okay, hun?!
Ah!
Lovely!
This sucks!
I hope they're having better luck!
Wonderful!
Ah!
Sweet spelling!
Look, merfolk are the only ones who don't eat meat!
Fishmen eat the stuff all the time!
So it's not like you can't get it here!
It's just not as common!
Yes!
That's great!
Man, it's about time one of them showed up!
Hey, taxi!
Hey, wait a minute!
Oh!
Vander Decken thought so!
But why is there a wanted poster for a ghost?
Yeah!
Wasn't this guy on the haunted ship we saw?
You saw him?
For real?
Uh-huh!
No way!
Whoa!
Our nation's been looking for him for years now!
The dude's a pirate and a no-good undersea thief!
I'll tell you all about it on the trip!
Let's load up!
And go!
Hey, taxi!
Hey, wait a minute!
Wait a minute!
Oh!
Vander Decken thought so!
But why is there a wanted poster for a ghost?
Yeah!
Wasn't this guy on the haunted ship we saw?
You saw him?
For real?
Uh-huh!
Let's load up!
And go!
Story goes, Vander Decken was hard up!
The guy was totally head over heels for the mermaid princess of the Ryugu kingdom!
He was so desperate, he sent love letters daily!
How shockery!
You know?
Gave up letters!
Started sending gifts instead!
Then threats!
Go to marry her!
A bee!
Feels great!
Ringy Bums!
Bums!
Oh!
Are you even listening to me?!
Sure!
Sorry about that!
Ahem!
Because his advances started to become so violent, the mermaid princess got scared!
And so, of course!
The stalker became a national concern!
Yeah!
But that was just the beginning!
Her father, King Neptune, got mad!
Which led to him sending the three princes you saw earlier off to hunt Vander Decken!
But even with the army, they can't find him.
Oh, come on, Kami. You stole all my thunder.
By the way, King Neptune's the god of the sea.
Plus, he's in control of this country.
If that's not enough responsibility, he has four children to take care of.
The mermaid princess is the youngest,
so obviously the three princes are the older kids in the royal family.
Please, I got this.
Great, but something still doesn't make sense.
Vanderdecken must be quite ancient.
If he isn't a ghost, I imagine he's a few hundred years old.
At least.
Huh. You're right, that doesn't make sense.
That is, unless you ignore the rumors.
Now, there's no denying that he existed,
but the truth of the matter is that the legendary sea captain Vanderdecken
died sometime after he arrived here on Fishman Island
and hasn't been heard from since.
That said, the ship you say you saw probably was the Flying Dutchman, but...
It's his descendant who's on board.
He's...
He's Vanderdecken the Ninth.
Wow, that's a lot!
Well, I have to say, it's a relief to find out he's not a ghost after all.
Believing we had come into contact with someone from the afterlife
was making me contemplate my own mortality.
And considering I'm a skeleton, I don't have much of that left.
I just wanted to tell an exciting story.
Man, I thought merfolk and fishmen all look the same,
but the more I see, the less they do.
Check out those old ones down there.
Their fins are split like Granny Kokoro.
See those babies? Right there.
Huh?
You'll notice the father is a fishman,
but the children are a mix of both species.
That's because when a mermaid and a fishman
love each other very much and decide to get busy,
their kids can come out looking like either parent.
Bam!
Four possibilities for the happy family.
Oh, that's why they all look different.
So cool.
All right, we finally made it to the highway.
Whoa!
This is fast!
What's up with that place?
Oh, nothing.
It's a candy factory.
Really?
Then why is there a pirate flag on it?
Oh, that?
That flag's everywhere here.
By the entrance and the harbor.
It's a big deal.
And for good reason at that,
it symbolizes that we're protected.
You see, the flag belongs to a famous pirate
named Charlotte Lin-Lin of the New World.
But she's better known as Big Mom,
one of the four emperors.
Whoa, that's no joke.
Back before the war in Marineford,
Whitebeard was this island's guardian.
But now that he's dead,
someone else had to take his place.
And that someone happened to be her.
Okay.
The thing is,
she demands a whole ton of candy
in exchange for her services.
Hence the factory that you just saw.
That's weird.
This country wouldn't be able to survive
without the protection of powerful people like her.
After all, this is a dangerous place
where pirates come and go.
And more often than not,
they aren't very friendly.
Yeah, I guess.
Plus, she's filling in where Whitebeard left off,
so that's gotta mean
she's a good person, doesn't it?
Depends on how you look at it.
Whitebeard never asked for anything
in return for his protection.
Big Mom, on the other hand,
treats it like a business
rather than a charity.
Still, that's cool.
An emperor.
Like shakes.
Crazy.
Hope they get to meet her.
Eyes forward.
This is where all the celebrity types live.
Fisperly Hills!
That tall building right in front
is Papa Goose's house,
where we're going.
All that?
For one starfish?
We have to do something.
We can't let this happen.
That's Madam Charlie,
from the cafe.
What's the matter?
Please, please tell us.
What's wrong?
Why are you upset?
Something must be done.
Now before it's too late.
Sure.
What do we do?
Find him!
The pirate boy in a straw hat!
It's an emergency!
He must leave the country!
Now!
There's no time!
Wait, you're having a premonition?
I swore I wouldn't use this power,
but something about that boy
felt off to me.
I...
I had no choice
but to look into the future!
What's going to happen?
Tell us, what did you see?
We have to know!
Charlie!
Tell us!
Madam!
Please!
I hope I'm wrong
and that
it won't happen.
I saw him clearly,
surrounded by flames.
Because of Straw Hat Luffy,
Fishman Island,
our country will be...
destroyed!
Beneath its dazzling exterior,
Fishman Island hides a dark history.
Harboring an age-old grudge,
the residents of the island prepare to take action.
Meanwhile, Luffy and friends cause a commotion at Papagoo's shop
and have an unexpected encounter with Neptune,
King of Fishman Island.
On the next,
One Piece,
the King of the Fishman Island,
Neptune,
the God of the Sea.
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!